* Products
    
        * [AccessPatrol
            
            USB Device Control](https://www.currentware.com/products/accesspatrol/)
        * [BrowseControl
            
            Web Filtering](https://www.currentware.com/products/browsecontrol/)
        * [BrowseReporter
            
            Employee Monitoring](https://www.currentware.com/products/browsereporter/)
        * [enPowerManager
            
            Power Management](https://www.currentware.com/products/enpowermanager/)
    * Overview
        
* Solutions
    
* Customers
    
    * Customer Success
        
* Resources
    
    * Featured Resources
        
    * More Resources

* Products
    
        * [AccessPatrol
            
            USB Device Control](https://www.currentware.com/products/accesspatrol/)
        * [BrowseControl
            
            Web Filtering](https://www.currentware.com/products/browsecontrol/)
        * [BrowseReporter
            
            Employee Monitoring](https://www.currentware.com/products/browsereporter/)
        * [enPowerManager
            
            Power Management](https://www.currentware.com/products/enpowermanager/)
    * Overview
        
* Solutions
    
* Customers
    
    * Customer Success
        
* Resources
    
    * Featured Resources
        
    * More Resources

**Note:** This policy applies to the use of the CurrentWare.com website. You may also be interested in [CurrentWare’s website terms of service](https://www.currentware.com/terms-of-service/).

For policies about the use of CurrentWare’s software please see the [CurrentWare software EULA](https://www.currentware.com/software-eula/) and the [CurrentWare software privacy policy.](https://www.currentware.com/software-privacy-policy/)

**Privacy Policy**
==================

**Last modified:** 11 December 2024

INTRODUCTION
------------

CURRENTWARE INC. (“Company” or “We”) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it by complying with this policy.

This policy describes:

* How we collect, use, disclose, and protect the personal information of our customers and website users (“you”).
* Describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website https://www.currentware.com/ (our “Website”).
* Our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

Privacy laws in Canada generally define “personal information” as any information about an identifiable individual, which includes information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person. 

This policy applies to information we collect, use, or disclose about you:

* On this Website.
* In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
* When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

The Website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins, services, social networks, or applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow the third party to collect or share data about you. If you follow a link to a third-party website or engage a third-party plugin, please note that these third parties have their own privacy policies and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. We do not control these third-party websites, and we encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit.

This policy DOES NOT apply to information that:

* We collect offline or through any other means, including on any other Company or third-party website (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), application, console, software or program created by the Company which is installed or accessed by you not from the Website.
* You provide to or is collected by any third party, through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from.
* You provide to, or is collected by your use of the CurrentWare Suite, BrowseReporter, BrowseControl, AccessPatrol, or enPowerManager (our “**Applications**“) which are subject to the End User License Agreement, Terms of  Use, and Applications Privacy Policy which are both provided and agreed to by you on your use of the Applications.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices for collecting, processing, and storing your information. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you indicate that you understand, accept, and consent to the practices described in this policy. This policy may change from time to time.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU
--------------------------------

We collect and use several types of information from and about you, including:

* Personal information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone number, Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet and any other identifier we may use to contact you (“personal information”). 
* Non-personal information, that does not directly or indirectly reveal your identity or directly relate to an identifiable individual, such as, demographic information, or statistical or aggregated information.
* Technical information, including your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform, or information about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website, and usage details.
* Non-personal details about your Website interactions, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URLs), clickstream to, through and from our Website (including date and time), products you viewed or searched for, page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), methods used to browse away from the page, or any phone number used to call our customer service number.

HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU
------------------------------------

**Information You Provide to Us** 

The information we collect directly from you on or through our Website may include:

* Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of contacting sales, contacting customer service, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website.
* Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses) if you contact us.
* Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.
* Your search queries on the Website.
* Because this site is protected by reCAPTCHA and we use Google Web Fonts, the Google [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms) apply.

**Information We Collect Through Cookies and Other Automatic Data Collection Technologies**  

When you visit or log in to our website, cookies and similar technologies may be used by our online data partners or vendors to associate these activities with other personal information they or others have about you, including by association with your email or online profiles. We (or service providers on our behalf) may then send communications and marketing to these emails or profiles. You may opt out of receiving this advertising by visiting [https://warmly.ai/p/do-not-sell-share-my-data](https://warmly.ai/p/do-not-sell-share-my-data)

We may use cookies or other automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

* Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
* Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

We may also use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). To learn more or to opt-out of tailored advertising please visit Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada Opt-Out Tool for information on how you can opt out of behavioral tracking on this Website and how we respond to web browser signals and other mechanisms that enable consumers to exercise choice about behavioral tracking.

The information we collect automatically is statistical information and may include personal information or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

* Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
* Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
* Speed up your searches.
* Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

* Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. 
* Web Beacons. Pages of our Website may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). 

HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
---------------------------

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

* To present our Website and its contents to you.
* To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
* To fulfill the purposes for which you provided the information or that were described when it was collected, or any other purpose for which you provide it.
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts with you, including for billing and collection or to comply with legal requirements.
* To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
* To improve our Website, products or services, marketing, or customer relationships and experiences.
* To measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you.
* To provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.
* To screen for potential risk or fraud.
* For any other purpose with your consent.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION
------------------------------

We may disclose aggregated information about our users as permitted by law.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

* To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
* In accordance with applicable law, to a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by the Company about our customers and users is among the assets transferred.
* To advertisers and advertising networks that require the information to select and serve relevant advertisements to you and others.
* To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business (such as analytics and search engine providers that assist us with Website improvement and optimization) and who are contractually obligated to keep personal information confidential, use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them, and to process the personal information with the same standards set out in this policy.
* To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. 
* For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
* With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

* To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request, in accordance with applicable law.
* To enforce or apply our terms of use \[LINK TO WEBSITE’S TERMS OF USE\] and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our customers, or others. 

CHOICES ABOUT HOW WE USE AND DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION
------------------------------------------------------

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

Targeted Advertising. You can opt out of targeted advertising by visiting: 

* FACEBOOK – [https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads](https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads)
* GOOGLE – [https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous/](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous%5C)
* BING – [https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads](https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads)
* Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  [http://optout.aboutads.info/](http://optout.aboutads.info/).

Opting out of a network does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. It does mean that the network from which you opted out will no longer deliver ads tailored to your web preferences and usage patterns.

DATA SECURITY
-------------

The security of your personal information is very important to us. We use physical, electronic, and administrative measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. 

DATA RETENTION
--------------

Except as otherwise permitted or required by applicable law or regulation, we will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. Under some circumstances we may anonymize your personal information so that it can no longer be associated with you. We reserve the right to use such anonymous and de-identified data for any legitimate business purpose without further notice to you or your consent. 

ACCESSING AND CORRECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
--------------------------------------------------

By law you have the right to request access to and to correct the personal information that we hold about you.

Applicable law may allow or require us to refuse to provide you with access to some or all of the personal information that we hold about you, or we may have destroyed, erased, or made your personal information anonymous in accordance with our record retention obligations and practices.

We will provide access to your personal information, subject to exceptions set out in applicable privacy legislation. 

If you are concerned about our response or would like to correct the information provided, you may contact us at info@currentware.com.

WITHDRAWING YOUR CONSENT
------------------------

Where you have provided your consent to the collection, use, and transfer of your personal information, you may have the legal right to withdraw your consent under certain circumstances. To withdraw your consent, if applicable, contact us at [info@currentware.com](mailto:info@currentware.com) Please note that if you withdraw your consent we may not be able to provide you with a particular product or service. We will explain the impact to you at the time to help you with your decision. 

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
-----------------------------

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you through a notice on the Website home page. 

We include the date the privacy policy was last revised at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date, active, and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

CONTACT INFORMATION AND CHALLENGING COMPLIANCE
----------------------------------------------

We welcome your questions, comments, and requests regarding this privacy policy and our privacy practices. Please contact us at: 

[](mailto:info@currentware.com)CurrentWare Inc.

92 Wanita Road

Mississauga, ON

L5G 1B8

Canada

We have procedures in place to receive and respond to complaints or inquiries about our handling of personal information, our compliance with this policy, and with applicable privacy laws. To discuss our compliance with this policy please contact us using the contact information listed above.

CurrentWare's data loss prevention, productivity, and security software gives you advanced control and visibility over technology use in your organization

* Learn
* Resources
        * DEMOS
* Company

©2024 CurrentWare. All Rights Reserved. Based in North America

|

|

|

This website uses cookies to improve your user experience. By using our website, you consent to all cookies in accordance with our [Privacy Policy](https://www.currentware.com/privacy-policy/)

[Learn More](https://www.currentware.com/privacy-policy/)Accept All
